(Amy:)The monkey in my tobacco study
has taken to smoking a pipe.
(Amy:)I'm supposed to remove his brain
to examine...
(Amy:)...but it's hard, because now
he reminds me of my uncle.
(Amy:)You've been awfully quiet tonight.
Is everything okay?
(Sheldon:)I'm fine.
(Amy:)All right. Well, how was work today?
(Amy:)Did you exchange your research
with Kripke?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Amy:)Sheldon, what's going on?
(Sheldon:)I read his research and...
(Sheldon:)...it's leaps and bounds ahead of mine.
(Sheldon:)Which means the mommy
of the smartest physicist at the university...
(Sheldon:)...is not my mommy as I had thought.
(Sheldon:)It's his mommy.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I wish there was something
I could do to make you feel better.